<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Intro | v train]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.vtrain.asia/blog/categories/intro/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.vtrain.asia/"/>
  <updated>2016-02-21T05:32:21+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://www.vtrain.asia/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[vtrain]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[support@vtrain.asia]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.vtrain.asia/blog/2016/02/17/main/"/>
    <updated>2016-02-17T07:49:54+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://www.vtrain.asia/blog/2016/02/17/main</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>At Vtrain.asia we are a bunch of guys skilled to provide corporate trainings on varitey of technical subjects.</p>

<p>We provide complete training courses designed to provide a complete overview of a particular topic, or courses customised to suit your needs.</p>

<p>Our training material is divided into a great many ‘modules’ – each lasting between ½hr and 6 hours (typically 1-2 hours) – so that they can easily be combined to create training courses that are tailored specifically to the needs of each individual customer.</p>

<p>The lists on this website give an idea of what modules we have available. Detailed contents lists for our modules are available on request. Don’t expect to get more than 6 hours of modules in one training day, even without any discussion sessions. We may have modules that are not yet listed, or we may be able to modify a module (or create a new one) to better meet your needs. So please get in touch to discuss your specific requirements.</p>

<p>In-house training courses are more effective than public courses because we can use examples that apply directly to the products/systems/installations concerned. We encourage delegates to bring examples or drawings they want to discuss. This makes the courses much more relevant.</p>

<p>We charge a fixed fee (plus expenses) for up to 15 participants – so the cost for 5 or more participants is usually less than available public courses (that aren’t as valuable anyway).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
